Guide to the Carole Hyatt Papers 1947-2006 (bulk, 1980s-1990s) MS 3105
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Audiotapes, 1975-2003, undated; 8 Linear feet
  - Subseries III.A. Audiotapes, Digitized, 1975-2003, undated; 6 Linear feet (457 cassette tapes in 6 boxes; 1.09 terabytes of digital files)
    - Feinberg, Mortimer; Walsh, Michaela (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 217)
      On Side 1: Walsh is at "head of tape, 5 min." followed by Feinberg, who is also on Side 2. Rest of Walsh is possibly on item 392. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Fenandez, Manny [Manuel] (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 214-215)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Ferarro, Geraldine (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 225)
      "Side 1 only." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Ferguson, Esther (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 218)
    - Fingerhut, Bert (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 223)
      "Stock broker, conservationist. 1 side and notes." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Fletcher, John (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 181)
    - Friedman, Ed (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 224)
      "prod [producer?]" Labeled on both sides of tape. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Gardner, Charles; Earl [Eul?], Jean (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 220)
      "Charles Gardner, Side 2. Small portion Jean Eul[?]"
    - Glankoff, Peter (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 431)
      "Cue story" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Glaser, Milton (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 430)
    - Good Morning (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 059)
    - Gowdy, Miya (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 129)
      Labeled on both sides. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Gray, Thomas A.; Bacca, Polly; Echols [or Ekeld], Evelyn (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 230)
      Side 1 is labeled with Gray first with a 3, perhaps implying this is the concluding side of another tape. Polly Bacca follows "1/2 tape in." Side 2 opens with Bacca "1/8, Colorado [pollution?]" then Echols/Ekeld. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Green, Steven (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 085)
    - Greenspon, Bill (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 128)
      "[word?], art dealer, artist. 1 side only." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Gschwandther, Laura (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 127)
    - Heavenrich, Charley (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 159)
    - Herzslinger, Reginald (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 222)
    - Heyman, Alice (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 221)
    - Hightower, John (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 238)
    - Hird, Neil; Hayes(?), Orville and Sarah (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 103)
      Side 1 includes Hird: "on snore(?), dir. - Odyssey." Side 2 includes the Hayes, likely noting their age as "70's, 76"). [Per index, re: Wisdom]
    - Hughes, Michele (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 236-237)
      "search firm." Labeled on three sides of two tapes. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Hungary, Budapest (Tape I) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 029)
      [Per index, re: 1992 women's group on women and careers?]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 026)
      "Chapter designations." [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 099)
      Noted on both sides of tape: "Marketplace." Likely continues with item 100. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 121)
      Side 1: "Corrections for Stuck Ch. 2." Side 2: Has "Helen H. 'Gears'" struckthrough and replaced with "Reuse", so it is not clear whether the second side of the tape has content or not. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 157)
      "Changing." [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 158)
      "Changing Revisions" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 244)
      Side 1: "phone tape." Side 2: "Carole H / Sorting Out." Possibly continues on item 245. [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 245)
      Side 1: "Carole, 3, Sorting out." Side 2: "2." Possibly continuation from item 244. [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 246)
      Both sides labeled "Carole" and numbered 1 and 2.
    - Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 247)
    - Hyatt, Carole. "Chapter Breakdowns" (3 tapes/6 files), undated (Box T3, Item 168-170)
      All 6 sides of 3 tapes are labeled. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole. "Presentation" (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 171)
      [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole. Book 1: Why Different, etc. (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 376)
    - Hyatt, Carole. Letter to Linda (1 tape/1 file), undated (Box T5, Item 395a)
    - Hyatt, Carole. M.O. & Sorting Out chapters (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 286)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, though the second side only refers to "sorting out." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole. M.O. & Types chapters (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T4, Item 287-288)
    - Hyatt, Carole. Triggers chapter (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 285)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Hyatt, Carole; Hiroko (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 100)
      Side 1: "Carole/Marketplace cuts" which likely is continuation of item 099. Side 2: "Hiroko"
    - Hyatt, Carole[?] (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 423)
      "In the Beginning, luncheon speech." Starts about halfway through first side of tape; see Poindexter below.
    - Hyler, Joan (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 235)
      "Permission to quote." Dated 10/17 on label. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Irv [Chicago School Study Interviews] (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 401)
      The Chicago School title, which was used for the digital file name, comes from a post-it in the cassette box. Several tapes were identified during digitization as related to this same study, but there is no indication on the tapes themselves that they relate. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447. For this tape 401, the label on side 1 of the tape itself reads only "Irv"; see Irv (item 446) for likely continuation.
    - Irv A. (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 446)
      Several tapes were identified somehow during digitization as related to "Chicago School Study Interviews." But there is no indication on the tapes or their case themselves that they relate. It is possible that the linking documentation was lost during the digitization process. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447. For this tape 446, the label on side 1 of the tape itself reads only "Irv A cont"; see Irv (item 401) for likely first part.
    - Jackson, Tom (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 156)
      "Outplacement" "Side 2: 3/4 side." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Johnson. Cynthia (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T3, Item 160-161)
      "Columbia[?]" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Jones, Christopher (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 146)
      "1 hour" on 90 minutes tape. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kagan, Diane; Merrill, Josephs (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 145)
      Side 1 has both Kagan and Josephs names. Side 2:" Diane Kagan-no notes-no release." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kelly, Nick (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 142-143)
      Kelly's name was also rendered as Kelley when the tapes were digitized and files named. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kiev, Ari (Dr) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T3, Item 234)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. Side 2: "1/2" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Kitrilakis, Sotiris (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 049)
    - Knerr, Tony (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 152)
      "External to internal journey" "Side 2: 1/2 side." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Koch, Gail (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 151)
      "Entrepeneur." Tape labeled on both sides. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Kraselsky, Louis Jeffrey; Kraselsky, Bruce (2 tales/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 149-150)
      Label on tape 1 (item 149) appears to indicate that Louis Kraselsky is "35, space architect" and that Bruce Kraselsky is "32, space lawyer." The second tape label (item 150) only refers to Bruce, with the note "tape may not work." [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Krebwich, Deborah (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T2, Item 147-148)
      Krebwich's name was also rendered as Krenwich when the tapes were digitized and files named. Label on tape 148 reads, in part,"to profit"; rest of label is illegible. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - [Kurt?] (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 383)
      The tape is unlabeled. It is unclear where the reference to "Kurt" comes from but it was assigned to the digital file names during digitization.
    - La Quita, Henry. (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 064)
      On side 1: "28 yrs. Blk. Do not type first 15 min." On side 2: "type all on this side" "incompletely typed". During the digital file naming process the name "La Quita, Henry" was rendered as "Henry, Anita". [On index, re: getting older]
    - Le Trombetta (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 418)
      "Shifting Gears." Labeled on both sides of the tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Liazos (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 457)
    - Lundberg, Barbara (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 415)
    - Mankin, Roxanne (2 tapes/3 files), undated (Box T6, Item 416-417a)
      "SF. Real Estate" Labeled on both sides of the first tape (item 416) and the first side of the second tape (item 417). The Mankin material taped over other recordings, which were struckthrough on the label, so those things might still be on the tape to some extent. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Marini, James (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 420)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted as "1/2 side" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Matthews, Rachel (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 107)
      "Atlanta." Labeled on both sides. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - McGovern, George (Senator) (2 tape/4 files), undated (Box T6, Item 413-414)
      Both tapes labeled on one side only. The relation between the two tapes, if any, is not clear. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Melia, Michael (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 438)
      Labeled "side 3" and "side 4". Sides 1 and 2 not found. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Monari [or Manari], Lou (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 435)
      "HR. NJ. 1 side only"
    - Moore, Alphyn (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T4, Item 294-295)
      Labeled on all four sides of two tapes. Second side of first tape (item 294) label appears to indicate that only 2 minutes are on it. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Moore, Lou (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 361)
      "producer. 34 yrs." Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted "1/8 of tape." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Naylor, Penelope (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 362)
      "do not use name." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - NJ Devils (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 363)
      "Bob Butera, Asst Coach. Dr. Fisher, on the [illegible] surgeon." "Side 1 only." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - O'Connell, Kevin (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T5, Item 359-360)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes; the third side notes "1/4 side". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - O'Connor, Dagmar (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 374)
      "sex therapist." Both sides labeled, with second noted as "1/4." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Peluzzi, Jeanne (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 382)
      Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted as "1/8". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Poindexter, Sharon (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T6, Item 422-423)
      First tape (item 422) is labeled on both sides. Second tape (item 423) is labeled on first side: "Sharon Poindexter, 1/2 tape). [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Previn, Dory (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 298)
    - Quilligan, Maureen (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 341)
      Yale [University]. failure to get tenure." Side 2 noted as "1/2 tape." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Rappaport, Dennis (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 437)
    - Rasa, Lisa; Barnett, Beth (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 304)
      "Lisa Rasa: bridal shop, Nashville" [On index, re: Shifting Gears]. "Beth Barnett: chiropractor, health"
    - Reemstma, Keith (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 331)
    - Reinisch, June (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 101)
      "Kinsey Institute. 1.5 sides"
    - Richter, Dick (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 052)
      "ABC - Common Ques. Interview." Side 2 is labeled "blank". [On index, re: radio interviews]
    - Roberts, Rennie (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 324)
      "Sr VP, American Express, human resources." Labeled on both sides, with second side noted as "1/8". During digitization, the file name used "Irene" rather than "Rennie." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Rose, Jackie (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 303)
      "teacher/spiritual" "master transition" "side 1 only". Jackie Rose was name used on tape label; business card in cassette container refers to name as Jacqueline Rose, which was name used to name digital file. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Rose, Leslie (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 280)
      "career counselor." Second side labeled as "1/4". [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Rosen, Estelle (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 326)
      "CSW". Both sides labeled with second side noted as "1/3". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Rosen, Jon (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 302)
    - Rosenthal, Philip (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 281)
      Possibly part of Rosenthal item 301. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Rosenthal, Philip (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 301)
      "T.V. Fanfare"[?] "Side 2, approx 10 mins". Possibly part of Rosenthal item 281. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Ross, Jane (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 330)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. During digitization, the file name incorrectly used "Jayne" rather than "Jane." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Rossman, Marge (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 389)
      Labeled on both sides of the tape, with the second side noted as "1/3". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Roth, Allie (3 tapes/6 files), undated (Box T4, Item 277-279)
      First tape (item 277) labeled on only one side, second tape (item 278) labeled on both sides, third tape (item 279) labeled on one side. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Rubenfeld, Ilana (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 390)
    - Rue, Wendy (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 391)
      "Side 1 only". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Rue, Wendy; Walsh, Michaela (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 392)
      "Wendy Rue, 2nd interview" is on both sides of tape. The first side also has "Michaela Walsh, 2nd half"; the first portion is possibly on item 217. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Russo, Julie; Lukins, Sheila (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 105)
      "Tape 1". See item 98, possibly for second half. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Russo, Julie; Lukins, Sheila(?) (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T2, Item 098)
      "Silver palate." See item 105, possibly for first half. [On index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Salzman, Bert. Interview (1 tape/1 file), undated (Box T5, Item 395b)
    - Sandlin Concepts. "The Shadow Dance" Virginia Sandlin (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 017)
      Possibly a commercially-produced tape by Sandlin. [On index, re: motivation tapes]
    - Schifter, Peter Mark (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T5, Item 364-365)
      Labeled on all four sides of two tapes. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Schwartz, Barbara (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 283)
    - Schwartz, Bob (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 368)
      Labeled on both sides of tape. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail] [Per index, re: Shifting Gears]
    - Schwartz, Morrie (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 314)
      Labeled on both sides of tape.
    - Selling Games (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 024)
      Dated on tape as Dec 1.
    - Shanks, Ann (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 369)
      "1/2 side 1 only". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Shirer, William (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 370)
      "fill in details." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Sieloff, Norman (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 393)
      "Policeman". Labeled on both sides. During digitization the name "Sieloff, Alice" was added to the digital file name, though it does not appear on the tape's label. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Smart People Revisited (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 013)
      "Thomas, Nick; Unger, Stewart; Sledoer, Helane; Hamlin, Sonya; Parks, Alexis". Dated as 6/9.
    - Snyder (Glankoff), Wendy (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 075)
    - Snyder, Frank (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 339)
      "McGraw-Hill. use allies." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Snyder, Wendy (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 338)
    - Sokolin, Gloria (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 340)
    - Sperry, Ann (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 386)
      "No notes". Labeled on both sides of the tape, with the second side noted as "1/10 of side". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Spiro, Tina; Hyatt, Carole (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 387)
      Side 1: "Tina Spiro. Fail." Side 2: "Carole Hyatt interviewed by Tina Spiro." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Stein (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T6, Item 443-444)
      Several tapes were identified somehow during digitization as related to "Chicago School Study Interviews." But there is no indication on the tapes or their case themselves that they relate. It is possible that the linking documentation was lost during the digitization process. The tapes so identified are items 401, 441, 442, 443, 444, 445, 446, and 447. For tapes tape 443-444, the labels on all four sides of the two tapes themselves read only "Stein".
    - Stern, Ari (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 384)
    - Switzer, Kathryne (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T4, Item 312)
      "marathoner." Labeled on both sides of tape. See also item 403 for likely continuation. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Switzer, Kathryne (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 403)
      Labeled as side 3 and 4. Like continuation of Switzer item 312. Side 4 is noted as "1/8". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Tatum, Bill (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 407)
      Labeled as side 1 and side 2. See also Tatum at items 320-322. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Tatum, Bill (3 tapes/6 files), undated (Box T5, Item 320-322)
      First tape (item 320) is labeled "1/2 side" and "retape" on the first side, with nothing on label of second side. Second tape (item 321) is labeled on one side as "Side 3, 10 min delay" and "blank side" on the other. The third tape (item 322) is labeled "Bill Tatum-Side 4" on one side; the second side is labeled "9/7. Houston. 7:00" and is unclear if it relates to Tatum. See also Tatum on item 407. [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Taylor, David (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 404)
    - The New Verbal Architecture (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 016)
      Commercial product by The Resource Link.[On index, re: motivation tapes]
    - Thomas, Liz and Nick (2 tape/4 files), undated (Box T6, Item 410-411)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes. Included on Side 3 label: "Calif Mustard" [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Thompson, Marion (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 343)
      Labeled only on side 1, as "3/4 side". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Timmer, Sharon (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T6, Item 405-406)
      Labeled on three sides of two tapes; side 3 is "1/8 side". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Trockmorton, Joan (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 419)
      "Dir marketing [to] real estate." [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Unger, Stewart (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T5, Item 333-334)
      Labeled on three sides of the two tapes; side 3 is "1/3". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Warner Books Women's Success Pkg, Featuring Conversations with Authors: Carole Hyatt, Margaret Crispen, David King (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 054)
      Commercial product by StudioTime. 29:32
    - Weiss, Bob (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 456)
    - Wender, Ira (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T6, Item 433-434)
    - Widman, Denise (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 076)
      "Not sure if picked up. One side only." It is not clear if this tape is directly related to the following Widman tapes or not. [On index re: winning couples]
    - Widman, Denise (2 tapes/4 files), undated (Box T1, Item 077-078)
    - Winer, Susan (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T5, Item 377)
      "death of partner." Labeled on both sides of tape, with second side noted as "1/4 of tape". [Per index, re: When Smart People Fail]
    - Wolper, David (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 397)
    - Wozniak, Steve (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 398)
    - Yankelovich, Daniel (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T6, Item 399)
    - Zuker, Elaina. Time on Tape: Your Quick Guide to Time Management (1 tape/2 files), undated (Box T1, Item 015)
      Possibly a commercially-produced tape by Zuker. [On index, re: motivation tapes]
  - Subseries III.B. Audiotapes, Not Digitized, 1980-2003, undated; 2 Linear feet in two record cartons (214 tapes)
    The subseries holds 214 audiocassette tapes that have not been digitized. These are a mix of interviews conducted by Carole Hyatt, radio interviews, presentations by Hyatt, and some commercial products by other speakers. (The tapes were not listened to during processing; this description is based on the labels on the tapes.) The container list provides some additional detail on the individual tapes in the subseries.
    In addition to the audiotapes in this subseries, there are about 42 audiotapes that were found with transcripts, notes and other paper documents in Hyatt's files. These were left in place and can be found in Series II.A Interview Transcripts and Notes.